董卓主演脱口秀
两天来，全世界都在等唐纳德·特朗普决定是否接受
For two days now, the world has been waiting for Donald Trump to decide whether to accept
以色列发来的"对伊朗开战"邀请。
Israel's evite to go to war with Iran.
我们知道他已经看了，但还没回复"是否出席"。
We know he's viewed it, but he still has an RSVP.
我最讨厌这种情况了。
I hate it when that happens.
与此同时，这个问题已经在他的MAGA基本盘内部引发了另一场战争。
Now, in the meantime, the question has started a separate war inside his MAGA base.
今天，它爆发成了一场激烈辩论，交战双方是右翼阵营中
And today, it exploded into a heated debate between the two most likable and charming voices
最"可爱"、最"有魅力"的两个声音。
on the right.
一边是想对伊朗开战的泰德·克鲁兹。
On the one side is Ted Cruz, who wants war with Iran.
另一边是塔克·卡尔森，他觉得泰德·克鲁兹对伊朗屁都不懂。
And on the other is Tucker Carlson, who thinks Ted Cruz doesn't know shit about Israel.
顺便问一下，伊朗有多少人口？
How many people live in Iran, by the way?
我完全不知道人口数字。
I don't know the population at all.
不，我不知道人口。
No, I don't know the population.
你想推翻的那个国家有多少人口你都不知道？
You don't know the population in the country you seek to topple?
伊朗有多少人？
How many people live in Iran?
九千二百万。
92 million.
哦，该死，泰德·克鲁兹。
Oh, damn, Ted Cruz.
你是一双800美元的菲拉格慕船鞋吗？
Are you a pair of $800 Farragamo boat shoes?
塔克·卡尔森把你完爆了，老兄。
Tucker Carlson owned you, buddy.
泰德·克鲁兹的反应是："我知道人口数字。"
Ted Cruz was like, I know the population.
"给我一秒钟数一下，好吗？"
Just give me a second to count, okay?
"让我看看，有阿亚图拉。"
Let's see, there's the Ayatollah.
"那是一个。"
That's one.
"还有铁面颊，他也算拉丁裔。"
The Iron Cheek, too, is a Latin one.
"我不知道。"
I don't know.
"不。"
No.
如果你喜欢看泰德·克鲁兹被狠狠打脸，想再看一遍吗？
If you enjoyed seeing Ted Cruz get metaphorically punched in the face, how'd you like to see it again?
为什么这很重要，不管是九千万还是八千万还是一亿？
Why is it relevant, whether it will be because 90 million or 80 million or 100 million?
为什么这很重要？
Why is that relevant?
因为如果你对这个国家一无所知，我没说我一无所知
Because if you don't know anything about the country, I didn't say I don't know anything
关于它。
about it.
好吧，那边的种族构成是什么？
Okay, what's the ethnic mix abroad?
哦，不。
Oh, no.
不是种族构成问题。
Not ethnic mixes.
你可不想在种族构成问题上跟塔克·卡尔森硬碰硬。
You don't want to go toe to toe with Tucker Carlson on ethnic mixes.
那是他的拿手好戏。
That's his best subject.
看看可怜的泰德·克鲁兹。
Look at poor Ted Cruz.
他就像在说："我想找个朋友求助，拜托了。"
He's like, I'd like to photo-friend, please.
"哦，该死，我没有朋友。"
Oh, shit, I don't have any.
"昨晚在澳拜客有个服务员叫我'冠军'。"
I had a waiter last night at Outback and he called me champ.
"我可以打电话给他吗？"
Can I phone him?
你知道，我不敢相信我会这么说，但我开始为泰德·克鲁兹感到难过了。
You know, I can't believe I'm saying this, but I'm starting to feel bad for Ted Cruz.
加油泰德，你可以的!
So come on, Ted, you got this.
他们是波斯人，主要是什叶派。
They are Persians and predominantly Shia.
好的。
Okay.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
你对伊朗根本一无所知。
It's not even, you don't know anything about Iran.
好吧，我不是塔克·卡尔森那样的伊朗专家，他说他打电话来
Okay, I am not the Tucker Carlson expert on Iran, who says he's calling to go over
推翻政府，他打电话来推翻这个国家。
the government and he's calling to go over the country.
不，你对这个国家一无所知。
No, you don't know anything about the country.
这真是太棒了。
This is awsome.
你什么都不知道。
You don't know anything.
不，你什么都不知道。
No, you don't know anything.
我不在乎谁赢得这场打斗。
I don't care about who wins the fight.
我就是喜欢看打架。
I just like watching the fight.
这就像异形大战铁血战士，但不知怎么的更恶心。
It's like alien versus predator, but somehow more gross.
你可以看到这事儿吵得有多激烈了。
You can see how heated this is getting.
很明显，在"是否要推翻伊朗"这个问题上，MAGA阵营的分歧
Clearly, Maga is much more divided about whether to overthrow Iran than they were about
比他们当初在"是否要推翻美国"时还大。
whether to overthrow America.
我觉得这次采访里的每句话都演变成了文字游戏。
I think a little comment in this interview turned into a semantic battle.
我真的相信。
Really believe that.
我们今天正在执行军事打击。
We are carrying out military strikes today.
你刚才说"是以色列"。
You said Israel was.
对，有我们帮忙。
Right, with our help.
我说的是"我们"，是以色列在主导，但我们在支援。
I'm said we, Israel is leading them, but we're supporting them.
哦，你这可是爆了个大料啊，因为美国政府昨晚刚否认了，
Well, this, you're breaking news here because the US government last night denied the
国家安全委员会发言人亚历克斯·菲佛代表特朗普否认了我们
National Security Council spokesman Alex Pfeiffer denied on behalf of Trump that we were
代表以色列采取了任何进攻性行动。
acting on Israel's behalf in any offensive capacity.
现在，我们没有在轰炸他们。
Now, we're not bombing them.
是以色列在轰炸他们。
Israel's bombing them.
你刚才明明说"我们"了。
You just said we were.
我们也在支援以色列。
We are supporting Israel as well.
我们？
We?
我？
I?
你？
You?
对于一个承诺在"代词"问题上绝不搞混的政党来说，这可真是够混乱的了。
For the party that promised no confusion around pronouns, this is really confusing.
重点是，MAGA世界正在疯狂内斗，所有人都在等着特朗普
The point is, Maga World is tearing itself apart and everyone is waiting for Trump to
做决定。
make a decision.
记住，特朗普突然退出了G7峰会，就为了火速赶回白宫，
And remember, Trump abruptly left the G7 summit so he could rush back to the White House, meet
和他的国安团队在战情室开会，然后决定是否要
with his National Security team in the situation room and decide if he's bringing America into
把美国拖入这场战争。
this war.
所以，我们都在等那个重磅官宣。
So, we were all waiting for the big announcement.
然后，它来了。
And then it came.
特朗普在"真相社交"上发帖说："我非常荣幸地宣布，我将会
Trump said in a truth social post, it is my great honor to announce that I will be putting
在白宫的两侧，也就是南草坪和北草坪上，竖起两根漂亮的旗杆。"
up two beautiful flag polls on both sides of the White House and North and South Lawns.
是的，这绝对算是个"官宣"。
Yes, that is definitely an announcement.
虽然不是我们等的那个，但行吧，在白宫装几根旗杆就装吧。
Not the announcement we were waiting for, but sure, have a couple flag polls installed
在白宫。
at the White House.
这样当您在战情室里忙着处理更重要的大事时，
That will be something for the groundskeepers to take care of while you're busy in the
园丁们也总算有活儿干了。
situation room dealing with more important matters.
"11点钟我们会升旗，但我们现在先把杆子立起来，然后他们
At 11 o'clock we're lifting the flag, but we're going to lift the poll now and then they
再去另一边。"
go into the other side.
"好的。"
Okay.
"但我会亲自到场介绍整个过程。"
But I'd be out there introducing the whole thing.
"现在，回到战情室。"
Now, back to the situation room.
"所以大楼这边会有一根。"
So we'll have one on this side of the building.
"那一边也有一根，位置都摆得很好。"
We'll have one on that side of the building properly placed.
"这些是全美国，不，实际上是全世界最棒的旗杆。"
These are the best polls anywhere in the country, in the world, actually.
"它们是锥形的。"
They're tapered.
"顶部也很漂亮。"
They have the nice top.
"我不知道你们这些人有没有审美。"
I don't know if you people are aesthetic.
"你们知道他们是假新闻。"
You know they're the fake news.
"那个我不好说。"
I don't know about it.
"我不了解他们。"
I don't know there.
"但对我来说，这是个非常激动人心的项目。"
But it's a very exciting project to meet.
这到底是什么情况？
What's going on here?
感觉就像有人跟他说："先生，您在'民调'里的数据不太好看。"
Feels like someone told him, sir, you're not doing well in the polls and he was like,
然后他回答："我听到了，我这就处理。"
I hear you, I'm on it.
话说回来，他那句关于"假新闻"不懂旗杆
And by the way, what was that aside about how the fake news doesn't understand flag poll
美学的话是什么意思？
aesthetics?
我的天，这简直是给自由派媒体创造了一个全新的刻板印象。
I mean, this is a whole new stereotype of the liberal media I didn't even know about.
"他们整天纠结于亨特·拜登的笔记本电脑，而且对锥形旗杆完全不懂欣赏。"
They live on 100 Binds laptop and they have no appreciation for tapered flag polls.
不过，个人觉得特朗普总算给那根50英尺长、
Now, personally, I think it's cool that Trump found a new use for the 50-foot poll that
梅拉尼娅拒绝碰的长杆找到了新用处，还挺酷的。
Melania refuses to touch him with.
他显然玩得很开心，尽管他还是克制住了自己，没让自己太
He was clearly having a good time, although he stopped himself from getting too carried
得意忘形。
away.
"让我们来一次体面的，他们叫它'升举'。"
Let's have a good, they call it a lifting.
"他们也用另一个词，不过我可不用那个词。"
They also use another word, but I'm not going to use that word.
"你知道是哪个词吧？"
You know that is?
"那个词是以E开头的。你们知道是什么词吧？"
The word starts with an E. You know what the word is?
"我要是用了，你们这帮人早就把我轰出去了。"
If I haven't used it, I'd be run out of town by you people.
"好吧，那就好好享受吧。"
All right, so enjoy it.
拜托，唐纳德。
Come on, Donald.
你以为如果你说"勃起"这个词，我们就会像小孩子一样
You think if you say the word erection, we're going to all act like children and take it
断章取义吗？
out of context.
我是说，拜托。
I mean, come on.
拜托。
Come on.
你从哪儿得出这种愚蠢的想法的？
Where'd you get a silly idea like that?
我要来了。
I'm going to come.
好的，各位。
Okay, y'all.
现在我想起来了，对吧。
Now I remember, right.
特朗普突然对说"勃起"这个词变得小心翼翼，真是太疯狂了。
It's crazy for Trump to suddenly get all worried about saying erection.
他的竞选结束语是"投票给我。"
His closing campaign message was vote for me.
"我见过阿诺德·帕尔默那令人难以置信的阴茎。"
I saw Arnold Palmer's incredible penis.
但好吧，你出来了，你谈论了旗杆，你见了旗杆工人，你
But okay, you came out, you talked about flag polls, you've met the flagpole guys, you
开了一些跟旗杆有关的老二笑话，是时候转身回屋里
made some flagpole-related dick jokes, time to turn around, go back inside and stop and
停止或升级这场战争了。
or escalate this war.
咱们别再浪费时间了。
Let's not waste any more time.
你们可以随便说拜登什么。
Say what you want about Biden.
他支持开放边境。
He was it for open borders.
他不支持人人都变性。
He wasn't for transgender for everybody.
"我们不知道这是从哪儿来的，先生。"
We don't know where it's coming from, sir.
"我说，看看关税。"
I said, check out the tariffs.
"他一天后打电话回来。"
He calls back about a day later.
"哇。"
Wow.
"在这群人里的某个地方，有人会吸引某个电影制片人，不是
Somewhere in this group, somebody that is going to captivate some movie producer, not
每个星期三。"
every Wednesday.
"唯一太晚的是鲍威尔。"
The only thing too late is Powell.
"鲍威尔太晚了。"
Powell's too late.
"太晚了，伙计。"
Too late, pal.
"我们吃晚饭吧。"
Let's have dinner.
"太晚了。"
Too late.
"你有没有遇到过一个不聪明的人，然后你在应付他。"
You ever have a guy that's not a smart person and you're dealing with it.
"任何合法移民？"
Any legal immigrant?
"35个俱乐部冠军。"
Thirty-five club championships.
"你们都知道这个。"
You all know that.
"35个俱乐部冠军。"
Thirty-five club championships.
"日用品价格下降了，鸡蛋价格下降了，你知道，鸡蛋。"
Groceries are down, eggs are down, you know the eggs.
"你知道每当他们谈论加文·纽森时我会怎么做吗？"
You know what I do whenever they talk about Gavin Newskin?
"我说，看看真实的。"
I say, look at the real.
"奥地利有非常非常易燃的奶酪。"
Austria has very, very flammable cheese.
我的天啊。
Good Lord.
我不想说什么，但如果你的旗杆"勃起"持续超过四小时，
I don't want to say anything, but if your flagpole erections last more than four hours,
你可能需要看医生了。
you probably want to see a doctor.
唐纳德。
Donald.
专注。
Focus.
专注，专注，专注。
Focus, focus, focus.
回到旗杆，保罗。
Get back to the flag, Paul.
不对。
No way.
回到战争。
Get back to the war.
我是说，战争。
I mean, war.
他把我都搞混了。
He's got me all mixed up.
谁来问问他关于战争的事。
Just someone, ask him about the war.
你有没有回答过关于你是否正在接近或者你是否相信美国
Have you even answered questions about whether you are moving closer or you believe the US
正在接近打击伊朗核设施的问题？
is moving closer to striking Iranian nuclear facilities?
你对此的想法是什么？
Where's your mindset on that?
我可能会做。
I may do it.
我可能不会做。
I may not do it.
我是说，没有人知道我要做什么。
I mean, nobody knows what I'm going to do.
对。
Right.
超级有用。
Super-helpful.
谢谢，老兄。
Thanks, guy.
这就是整件事的关键。
That is the key to this whole thing.
没有人知道他想做什么，包括唐纳德·特朗普自己。
Nobody knows what he wants to do, including Donald Trump.
他宁愿做家庭装修项目，也不想弄清楚如何收拾他所有的
You'd rather be doing home renovation projects than figure out how to fix all his
烂摊子。
f**ks.
说实话，我赞成。
And honestly, I agree.
我觉得我们应该鼓励他把所有时间都花在园林绿化项目上，而不是
I think we should encourage him to spend all his time on landscaping projects as opposed
把美国拖入另一场中东战争。
to bringing America into another Middle East war.
坦率地说，很多人会因为这个决定而松一口气，甚至欣喜若狂。
Frankly, a lot of people would be relieved by that decision, even overjoyed.
这甚至可能给人们...
It might even give people...
我不想说出来，但它以"蛋"开头。
I don't want to say it, but it starts with an egg.